and the final recipient of the Asia's
most influential companies is none other
than the potential Vietnam credential
Vietnam Assurance recognizes one of the
Asia's most influential companies excels
in Revenue growth Innovation people and
CSR their Purpose Driven approach
prioritizes ESG considerations investing
in people and communities through
diverse initiative and core values of
like ambition curiosity empathy courage
and nimber us they transcend mere
financial goals emphasizing holistic
care and
impact so becoming an uh one of the Asia
most influential companies Prudential
Remains the people Centrics and it
impacts on the transformation journey to
remain The Purpose Driven organizations
and also the value L leader in the
market so I am very glad to be here
because as a HR we drive the work for
Transformations also the people grow in
the organization where we only are not
only focus in terms of the capabilities
but also in terms of the mentally and
the physically strong as
[Music]
well